Finding Aid for Philip A. Hart Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Subject files, 1959-1976; 96 linear feet
  - 1959-1964
    - Agriculture
      - Commodity Stabilization Service, Dept. of, 1961-1962 (Box 134)
      - Conservation Soil Bank, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Conservation Soil Bank, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Conservation Soil and Water, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Conservation Watershed Projects, 1962-1964 (Box 134)
      - Conservation Watershed Project, Jo Drain Watershed, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Co-ops, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Cotton, 1959-1964 (Box 134)
      - Cotton Surplus Paper Making, 1963-1964 (Box 134)
      - Dairy Farm Labor, 1960 (Box 134)
      - Dairy Program, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, Cherries, Red Tart and School Lunch Program, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, Corn Base Figures, Van Buren County, 1961 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, Ham, Watered, 1961-1962 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, Monocle Lake, 1960-1961 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, R.E.A., 1961-1963 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, R.E.A. cases, see separate folder, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Department Cases, Strawberry Tariff, 1961-1962 (Box 134)
      - Economic Research Service, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Estes, Billy Sol, Dept. of, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Farm Poverty, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program, 1963-1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program 1959 Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program 1960 Correspondence, 1960 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program 1961 Correspondence, 1961 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program 1962 Correspondence, 1962 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program, Crop Insurance, 1963-1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program, Dairy Price Supports, 1961-1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program, Emergency Feed Grain, 1963-1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program Price Supports, 1959 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program Price Supports, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Farm Program Price Supports, Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 134)
      - Farmers Home Administration, Dept. of, 1961-1963 (Box 134)
      - Feed Grain Program Payment, 1963-1964 (Box 134)
      - Food Stamp Program, Gogebic Co., 1962 (Box 134)
      - Foreign Service, 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - Forest Service, 1961-1963 (Box 135)
      - General, 1959-1962 (Box 135)
      - General, 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - General Announcements, 1960-1963 (Box 135)
      - Grapes, 1963 (Box 135)
      - Insects and Pests, Beetles-Japanese, 1961-1963 (Box 135)
      - Insects and Pests, Cereal Leaf Beetle, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - Insects and Pests, Pesticide Center, MSU, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Insects and Pests, Pine Root Collar Weevil, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Lamb Grading, 1959-1960 (Box 135)
      - Lettuce, 1962 (Box 135)
      - Loans, FHA, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Loans, Farm Ownership, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Loans, Recreational use of Farm, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Loans, Rural Resident Loan Program (Box 135)
      - Milk Marketing Order, 1962 (Box 135)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1963 (Box 135)
      - New Farm Bill, 1963 (Box 135)
      - Org., Farmers and World Affairs Incorporated, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Ottawa County, Forest Service, 1962 (Box 135)
      - Ottawa County Lands, Forest Service, 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - Packers and Stockyards Division, 1962 (Box 135)
      - Plant Disease, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Potato Acreage Control, 1961-1962 (Box 135)
      - Potatoes, 1960-1964 (Box 135)
      - Potatoes, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Poultry, 1962 (Box 135)
      - Poultry, 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - Poultry Inspect. Fees, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Poultry Research Facility, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Processing Plant, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Sault Ste. Marie Water Rights, 1963 (Box 135)
      - Services Economy Moves, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Soil Conservation, 1960-1962 (Box 135)
      - Soil Conservation Service, 1961-1962 (Box 135)
      - Subsides, 1960-1961 (Box 135)
      - Sugar, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - Sugar Beets, 1959-1963 (Box 135)
      - Surplus Food, 1959-1961 (Box 135)
      - Surplus Grain Storage, 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - Tobacco Price Support, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Wheat, 1961-1963 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Bill, 1963 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Bulgur Program, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Control Program, 1959-1962 (Box 135)
      - Wheat, Eastern Soft, 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Moisture Charts, 1959 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Program, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Referendum, 1963 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Referendum, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Wheat Standards, 1964 (Box 135)
    - Appropriations
      - Agriculture Conservation Program, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Agricultural Program, Cooperative Extension Service, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Agricultural Program, Market Facility Planning, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Defense, U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Fisheries, 1963-1965 (Box 135)
      - Forest Service, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - Forest Service Administration, 1964 (Box 135)
      - HEW, Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Offense Control Act. Extension, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - HEW, Mental Retardation and Medical Facilities, 1964 (Box 135)
      - HEW, Supplemental Voc. Education Funds, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Housing, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Independent Office, Fed. Power Commission, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Interior, National Park Service, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Legislative Branch, Library Service, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - National Academy of Science, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Peace Corps, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Pollution, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - Public Works, 1964 (Box 135)
      - School Lunch, 1964-1965 (Box 135)
      - Senate Fund, Items, Last Appropriation Bill, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Soil Conservation, 1963-1965 (Box 135)
      - State Department, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Supplemental S. 627, 1964 (Box 135)
      - Waterways, 1964 (Box 135)
    - Armed Services
      - General, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - Appropriations-Defense (Box 136)
      - Centralized Power, Secretary McNamara (Box 136)
      - Chaplains (Box 136)
      - Congressional Medal of Honor Society (Box 136)
      - Deactivation of Reserve Units (Box 136)
      - Defectors/Prisoners of War (Box 136)
      - Detroit Ordinance Tank and Automotive Command Complaints (Box 136)
      - Facilities (Box 136)
      - Germ and Chemical Warfare (Box 136)
      - Military Housing Units (Box 136)
      - Muskegon Ordnance Plant (Box 136)
      - New Defense Supply Agency (Box 136)
      - New Mobility Organization in Michigan, Includes OTAC (Box 136)
      - Ordnance Tank Automotive Command (Box 136)
      - Manpower Training Rep. of China (Box 136)
      - Prep. Draft (Box 136)
      - Prep Manpower, ROTC (Box 136)
      - Prep. Manpower Training and Lowering of Draft Age (Box 136)
      - Prep. Prod. Chemicals (Box 136)
      - Preparedness Prod. Weapons (Box 136)
      - Prep. Train. Viet-Nam (Box 136)
      - Real Estate, Grosse Ile (Box 136)
      - Real Estate, Lease, Grayling Army (Box 136)
      - Real Estate, Sale, GSA, Camp Lucas (Box 136)
      - Real Estate, Surplus Prop., Sage (Box 136)
      - Real Estate, Surplus Sale, Charity Island (Box 136)
      - Religious Discrimination in Certain Countries (Box 136)
      - Schools for Dependent Overseas (Box 136)
      - Security of Military Info (Box 136)
      - Selective Service System (Box 136)
      - Skilled Manpower (Box 136)
      - Training Lackland Air Force Base (Box 136)
      - Training Ship for Naval Reserve Training (Box 136)
      - Training Sundays (Box 136)
      - Air Force, General (Box 136)
      - Air Force, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Air Safety (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Big Brother Program (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Crawford, Robert (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Extension of the North-South Runway Selfridge Air Force (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Flying Objects (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Foto Video Electronics, Inc. (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Kincheloe, Sawyer Bases (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Minuteman Installation -- Missile Sites (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Manuals (Box 136)
      - Air Force, Mount Clemens and Selfridge AFB Water Rate Agreement (Box 137)
      - Air Force, Per Diem Payment for Temporary Duty (Box 137)
      - Air Force, Project 20-10 (Box 137)
      - Air Force, Selfridge Air Force Base Abolishment of 21 Civilian Positions (Box 137)
      - Air Force, Sonic Booms (Box 137)
      - Air Force, Turkey Police (Box 137)
      - Army, General (Box 137)
      - Army, 2 folders (Box 137)
      - Army, Acquisition Record of Leasing Space in Detroit --, February 2, 1962 (Box 137)
      - Army, Additional Divisions (Box 137)
      - Army, Bay City, Army Reserve Training Center (Box 137)
      - Army, Camp Lucas (Box 137)
      - Army, Declare Surplus -- Muskegon Ordnance Plant (Box 137)
      - Army, Dept. of Re-opening Pedestrian Gate at Ordnance Tank Automotive (Box 137)
      - Army, Dredging Ballards Reef and Livingston Channels and Canadian Labor. (Box 137)
      - Army, Enlargement of O'Rourke memorial US Army Reserve Center in Bay City (Box 137)
      - Army, Inactivation -- 422d Ordnance (Box 137)
      - Army, Nike Battery (Box 137)
      - Army Reorganization of the army (Box 137)
      - Army, S.I.P.R.E. Program (Box 137)
      - Army, Unrein, General (Box 137)
      - Coast Guard (Box 137)
      - Coast Guard, Ice Breaking in Green Bay Area (Box 137)
      - Coast Guard, Removal of Cutter Mackinaw From Cheboygan (Box 137)
      - Coast Guard, Sinking of the Carl W. Bradley (Box 137)
      - Coast Guard, Speed Regulations St. Clair River (Box 137)
      - National Guard Armories (Box 137)
      - National Guard and Reserve Realignment (Box 137)
      - National Guard Units (Box 137)
      - Navy, General (Box 137)
      - Navy (Box 137)
      - Navy, Film "Communism on the Map" (Box 137)
      - Navy, Reserve Unit Placement in Niles (Box 137)
      - Navy, Thresher Purchase (Box 137)
    - Atomic Energy
      - Nuclear Explosion Detection (Box 137)
      - Nuclear Testing (Box 137)
      - Nuclear Weapons (Box 137)
      - Nuclear Weapons Transfer (Box 137)
    - Budget
      - General (Box 138)
      - Bureau of the Budget (As it affects procurement in Michigan). (Box 138)
      - National Bureau of the Budget (Box 138)
      - National Bureau Executive Orders (Box 138)
      - National Needs, 1964 (Box 138)
    - Civil Rights
      - General
        - 1961-1962 (Box 138)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 138)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1962
        - Civil Rights Commission, 1961 (Box 138)
        - Demo Advisory Council Statement, 1959 (Box 138)
        - Freedom Riders, 1961 (Box 138)
        - Georgia-Albany, 1962 (Box 138)
        - Mississippi University Integration by James Meredith (Box 138)
        - Negro in American History (Box 138)
        - President's Comm., Equal Employment Opportunity, Mary C. Covington, 1962 (Box 138)
        - Walker, General at Mississippi University (Box 138)
        - Walsh, Judge Remarks, 1959 (Box 138)
      - Correspondence, 1963
        - Act Contrary to 14th Amendment, Text for Title III (Box 138)
        - Anti (Box 138)
        - Birmingham Bombing (Box 138)
        - Congratulations (Box 138)
        - Constitutional Rights and Equal Opportunity (Box 138)
        - Demonstrations (Box 138)
        - Education (Box 138)
        - Flint Hearings on Race Relations (Box 138)
        - Freedom Marches, Detroit, Washington, etc. (Box 138)
        - Freedom Walkers in Alabama (Box 138)
        - In The Armed Services (Box 138)
        - Ingalls Shipbuilding Co. (Box 138)
        - King, Rev. Martin Luther (Box 138)
        - Mich. Conf. with Federal Agencies (Box 138)
        - Mississippi (Box 138)
        - NAACP (Box 138)
        - No Fed. Funds to Programs Administered in Discriminatory. Manner (Box 138)
        - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunities (Box 138)
        - Poindexter-Hart at Commerce Committee (Box 138)
        - Pro (Box 138)
        - Racial Discrimination (Box 138)
        - Racial Discrimination in Federal Depts., Etc. (Box 138)
        - Racial Discrimination in the Building Trades in NYC. (Box 138)
        - Tragedy in Birmingham (Box 138)
        - Violence (Box 138)
      - Correspondence, 1964
        - General (Box 138)
        - Administrations Program (Box 138)
        - Alabama (Box 138)
        - Busing of Children (Box 138)
        - Civil Rights Commission (Box 138)
        - Community Relations Service (Box 138)
        - Council of Fed. Org. (Box 138)
        - Equal Employment Opportunities (Box 138)
        - FBI Role (Box 138)
        - Freedoms Guaranteed by Constitution (Box 138)
        - Freedom Walk (Box 138)
        - Mississippi/South (Box 138)
        - Prayer in School (Box 138)
        - Public Accommodations (Box 138)
        - Publications (Box 138)
        - State Rights (Box 138)
    - Commerce
      - Bureau of Census, Dept. of (Box 139)
      - Bureau of International Business Operations, S. Spilos-Worlds Fair in Detroit (Box 139)
      - Bureau of Public Roads (Box 139)
      - Commerce, Dept of, T.J. McCarthy Steamship Lines (Box 139)
      - Communications
        - FCC Free and Equal Time Re Debate on Proposed Constitution (Box 139)
        - FCC Gelderloos, Larson (Box 139)
        - Federal Communications Act, S. 1858, Sec. 315, S. 2424 (Box 139)
        - Narba and Mexican Treaties (Box 139)
        - Radio, 2 folders (Box 139)
        - Radio Freetime for Proponents of Opposite Views (Box 139)
        - Radio License, FCC (Box 139)
        - Television (Box 139)
        - TV Caliber of Prog. (Box 139)
        - TV Nixon Program of Howard K. Smith (Box 139)
      - Export Licensing, Dept. of (Box 139)
      - Federal Trade Commission, 2 folders (Box 139)
      - FTC, State Wide Carpet Company Carpet Swindle (Box 139)
      - Fisheries
        - Fisheries, 2 folders (Box 139)
        - Fish Meal Plant (Box 139)
        - Great Lakes (Box 139)
        - Lake Superior, ARA Loan (Box 139)
      - Foreign (Box 139)
      - Great Lakes Development (Box 139)
      - Great Lakes Senatorial Group (Box 139)
      - Imports, Educational and Cultural Material (Box 139)
      - Interstate (Box 139)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 139)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission, Trucking vs. Railroads (Box 139)
      - Maritime Administration (Box 139)
      - National Mediation Board Dispute with United Air Lines (Box 139)
      - New York World's Fair, 1964 (Box 139)
      - Olympics in Detroit See: Mich. State Info Detroit Olympics (Box 139)
      - Patent Office (Box 139)
      - Railroads (Box 139)
      - Savannah Situation (Box 139)
      - Trade
        - Exports, Soviet Union (Box 139)
        - Foreign Exemption Duty (Box 139)
        - Foreign Export (Box 139)
        - Foreign Export, Powdered Milk, Cuba (Box 139)
        - Foreign Export, Russia Wheat Sale (Box 139)
        - Foreign Imports -- Beef (Box 139)
        - Foreign Imports Glass (Box 139)
        - Foreign Private Trade Credit Sales (Box 139)
        - Imports, Beef Labeling (Box 139)
        - Imports, Curbs/Dairy Products (Box 139)
        - Imports, Foreign Cars (Box 139)
        - Imports, General (Box 139)
        - Imports, Iron Ore (Box 139)
        - Imports, Metals (Box 139)
        - Imports, Oil, 2 folders (Box 139)
        - Imports, Petro, 1962 (Box 139)
        - Imports, General (Box 139)
        - Imports, Residual Oil Quotas, 1963 (Box 140)
        - Imports, Sugar Quota (Box 140)
        - Trichloroethylene and other acids (Box 140)
        - Iron Curtain Countries (Box 140)
        - License Appli. Export (Box 140)
        - Reciprocal Rate Structures (Box 140)
        - Reciprocal Trade Brazil (Box 140)
        - Reciprocal Trade European Industrial Seminar (Box 140)
      - Trade Tariff
        - Duty offset operations, Canada (Box 140)
        - Imported Cars (Box 140)
        - Nylon fish Netting (Box 140)
        - Peat Moss (Box 140)
        - Peat Moss Thank Yous (Box 140)
        - U.S. Tariff Commission Duties for Cylinder, Crown and Sheet Glass-Cadillac Glass (Box 140)
        - U.S. Tariff Commission, Guardian Glass Company, Inc. Cylinder, Crown and Sheet Glass (Box 140)
      - Transportation
        - Air Bulk Airfreight (Box 140)
        - Air, Discontinuance of flight Service Station at Houghton (Box 140)
        - Air Travel to Cuba (Box 140)
        - Air, Federal Aviation Agency (Box 140)
        - Air, FAA, A.F. Holden Company (Box 140)
        - Air, FAA, Moving Detroit Air Route Traffic Control Center (Box 140)
        - Air, FAA Sonic Booms in Petoskey Area (Box 140)
        - Air, Jet Service West Coast (Box 140)
        - Air, Oakland County Airport (Box 140)
        - Airports, Caro Airport (Box 140)
        - Airports, Detroit Metropolitan Wayne County Airport (Box 140)
        - Airports, Frankfort Airport (Box 140)
        - Airports, Phelps Collins Airport, Alpena (Box 140)
        - CAB, Northeast Airlines (Box 140)
        - Ferries Mackinac (Box 140)
        - Houghton-Hancock Discontinuation of North Central (Box 140)
        - R.R. Disc. Of R.R. (Box 140)
        - R.R. Mergers Effect on Midwest (Box 140)
        - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 140)
        - St. Lawrence Seaway Detroit Port Facility (Box 140)
        - St. Lawrence Seaway, Utilization of, Served by Great Lakes Ports-Joe McCann (Box 140)
      - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 3 folders (Box 140)
    - Defense
      - Civil
        - Civilian Control (Box 141)
        - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Defense Mobilization, See OEP (Box 141)
        - Fall Out Shelters (Box 141)
        - OCDM, General (Box 141)
        - OCDM, Office of Emergency Planning (Box 141)
        - Senator Young's Remarks (Box 141)
      - National
        - General (Box 141)
        - ACDA Firearms (Box 141)
        - Arms Control and Disarmament -- S. Russia Correspondence, 1963 (Box 141)
        - Arms Control and Disarmament -- Phoenix Paper Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Civil Defense Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Consol. Of Install. Functions Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Defense Briefings, Industry Participation Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Defense Spending, Criticism Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Disarmament (Box 141)
        - Disarmament Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - Disarmament Negotiations, Fov. N. Rockefeller (Box 141)
        - Eliminate Waste in Procurement (Box 141)
        - Missile Gap (Box 141)
        - Nike-Zeus Program (Box 141)
        - Peace Movements (Box 141)
        - Test Ban (Box 141)
        - Test Ban Agreement (Box 141)
        - UFO Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
        - US Arms Control and Disarmament Agency (Box 141)
        - Vietnam, Gulf of Tonkin Correspondence, 1964 (Box 141)
    - Economy, National
      - Balance of Payments (Box 141)
      - Eco. Study, UPCAP (Box 141)
      - Eisenhower Article on Government Spending (Box 141)
      - Federal Aid to Communities (Box 141)
      - Fiscal Policy (Box 141)
      - Inflation (Box 141)
      - Loans, SBA, Comm. Fisheries (Box 141)
      - Loans, SBA, Kalkaska (Box 141)
      - National Debt (Box 141)
      - Problems Correspondence, 1963 (Box 141)
      - Problems, ARA, Service Area Report, CMU (Box 141)
      - Problems, Eco. Stu. Upper Midwest Region (Box 141)
      - Small Business (Box 141)
      - Small Business, Iroquois Corporation, SBA Loan (Box 141)
      - Standard Metro Stat. Area Ypsilanti/Detroit (Box 141)
      - Unemployment (Box 141)
      - War on Poverty Program (Box 141)
    - Education
      - Opposition to Federal Aid To Education (Box 141)
      - Parochial School, Financial Assistance (Box 141)
    - Federal Government
      - Adrian Air Force Plant Correspondence, GSA (Box 142)
      - Agencies, State vs. Fed. Investigations (Box 142)
      - Chrysler Corporation, SEC (Box 142)
      - Criticism
        - Agencies, U.S. Employ Service (Box 142)
        - CIA (Box 142)
        - Congress Inaction (Box 142)
        - Endorsement of Organ. By Senate Committee (Box 142)
        - NASA (Box 142)
        - State Dept., G.P.O. Embassy in Mexico City (Box 142)
        - Supreme Court (Box 142)
      - Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. (Box 142)
      - Federal Reserve System (Box 142)
      - Health, Education, and Welfare
        - General, 4 folders (Box 142)
        - 1963 (Box 142)
        - Cranberries (Box 142)
        - Detroit River Pollution (Box 142)
        - Food and Drug, 1963 (Box 142)
        - Lake Erie Pollution (Box 142)
        - Public Health, 1963 (Box 142)
        - Public Health Service Water Pollution in Great Lakes (Box 142)
        - Stilbestrol (Box 142)
        - Water Pollution, 2 folders (Box 142)
        - Water Pollution, Huron River (Box 142)
        - Water Pollution, Lake Erie (Box 142)
        - Water Pollution, Midwest Water Pollution Laboratory (Box 142)
        - Water Pollution, Monroe Area (Box 142)
      - HHFA-URA, Cynthia Nelsey (Box 142)
      - House Appropriations Comm. Statement of Sen. Hart to Subcom. HEW on Midwest Water Pollution Control Lab, at Ann Arbor, Michigan. (Box 142)
      - Justice Dept.
        - General, 3 folders (Box 142)
        - Anti-Trust US v. Chrysler (Box 142)
        - Attorney Generals Trip (Box 142)
        - FBI (Box 142)
        - Firearms (Box 142)
        - Food and Drug, William L. Plot (Box 142)
        - General Motors Monopoly Power (Box 142)
        - Hoffa, James (Box 142)
        - Increase in Gas Prices Investigation-Detroit (Box 142)
        - Justice Restricts State Prison Labor in Contracts with US Government (Box 142)
      - Menominee River Pollution, Public Health Service (Box 142)
      - Pay Raises Congressional, 2 folders (Box 143)
      - President Johnson Criticism (Box 143)
      - Proposed Federal Building, Ann Arbor, MI (Box 143)
      - Reorganization-Congressional Operations (Box 143)
      - Reorganization of Courts (Box 143)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box 143)
      - Treasury Dept.
        - General, 2 folders (Box 143)
        - Bureau of Customs (Box 143)
        - Bureau of Narcotics (Box 143)
        - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 143)
        - IRS, see Taxes (Box 143)
      - URA Open Space Program (Box 143)
    - Foreign Relations
      - Africa (Box 143)
      - Africa, Apartheid in South Africa (Box 143)
      - Africa, Congo, Stanleyville (Box 143)
      - Africa, Williams Trip (Criticisms of), 1961 (Box 143)
      - A.I.D.
        - Algeria (Box 143)
        - Alliance for Progress, Latin America (Box 143)
        - Birth Control (Box 143)
        - Chile (Box 143)
        - Countries Not Aligned with the West (Box 143)
        - Food for Peace (Box 143)
        - India (Box 143)
        - International Cooperation Admin. (Box 143)
        - Moslem Temple in Washington (Box 143)
        - United Arab Republic (Box 143)
      - Article on Cuba in "Our Sunday Visitor", 1959 (Box 143)
      - Asia, Communist China (Box 143)
      - Asia, South East, 1964 (Box 143)
      - Asia, Thailand (Box 143)
      - Asia, Tibet, Dalai Lama (Box 143)
      - China Olympics (Box 143)
      - Committee for non-violent Action (Box 143)
      - Congo Aid (Box 143)
      - Congo Katanga (Box 143)
      - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 143)
      - Criticisms Congressional Junkers (Box 143)
      - Cuba
        - American Owned Property (Box 143)
        - Communist Aggression in this Hemisphere (Box 143)
        - Guantánamo (Box 143)
      - Cyprus (Box 144)
      - Dulles (Box 144)
      - Egypt (Box 144)
      - Foreign Aid, 1959 (Box 144)
      - Foreign Aid, 1960 (Box 144)
      - Foreign Aid, 1961 (Box 144)
      - Foreign Aid, 1963 (Box 144)
      - Foreign Aid, 1964 (Box 144)
      - General, 1959 (Box 144)
      - General, 1960 (Box 144)